Arsenii Ashukha

Moscow, Russia • ⋈ ars.ashuha@gmail.com • ars-ashuha.ru • 23 years old ☺



Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT also I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT, MSU, HSE I teach several Machine Learning courses.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Hive, Linux, English (B2)

Education

2015 - 2017 Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: 9.0/10.0 Regularization of Deep Neural Nets, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT) Thesis



2015 - 2016 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0 Result Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian ML, Deep Learning, Machine Learning



2011 - 2015 Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Thesis Building of Uncorrelated Kernels for Topic Models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU)



Teaching

- Feb 2016 Feb 2017: Practical Lecturer of Machine Learning course at MIPT (parts 1,2)
- Sep 2016 Now: Lecturer of several classes of Deep Learning courses at MSU and HSE
- Oct 2016 Now: Lecturer of DL part of Data Mining in Action course, YouTube records in Russian 3
- Feb 2017 Now: Lecturer of DL part in Machine Learning course at MIPT
- Feb 2017 Now: Co-head of Scientific Machine Learning seminar for MIPT and HSE Yandex students

Experience

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

3 month - Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN

Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group (E. Krofto)

Yandex

Dec 2013 - Feb 2016

2 year 1 month p/t

Rambler, Moscow — R&D Engineer at ML Group (A. Gorokhov, P. Klemenkov)

- Improving the quality and performance of user classification using browser history

RAMBLER&Co

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013 3 month

Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group (M. Karpenko) - Users query classification to show a mixing in search results

- Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru

RAMBLER&Co

Publications

Dmitry Molchanov*, Arseniy Ashuha* and Dmitry Vetrov (* equal contribution)

Variational Dropout Sparsifies Deep Neural Networks https://arxiv.org/abs/1701.05369 (Under review by the ICML 2017)

Dmitry Molchanov, Arseniy Ashuha and Dmitry Vetrov

Dropout-based Automatic Relevance Determination Bayesian Deep Learning Workshop, Neural Information Processing Systems 2016

Arseniy Ashuha and Natalia Loukachevitch

Bigram Anchor Words Topic Model International Conference on Image Analysis, Social Networks and Texts 2016